我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来  我只是个普通的鉴证专员
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
我秘密地打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界也因此出现了新的威胁
but in doing so, I opened up our world to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》前情回顾
Previously on The Flash...
不
No!
拯救了中城的那个人
The man who saved Central City.
你为什么想杀我
Why did you want to kill me?
-他答应带我回家  -谁
- He promised he'd take me home. - Who?
-极速  -威尔斯杀了我妈妈
- Zoom. - Wells killed my mother.
我什么都不知道了
I don't know anything anymore,
尤其不知道谁可以相信
especially who I can and can't trust.
尖端科研实验室比以前更安全
S.T.A.R. Labs is now safer than ever.
这样就没人能随便进出了
People can't just waltz in and out of here.
没错
Exactly.
-站在那别动  -我叫杰伊·加里克
- Stay where you are. - My name is Jay Garrick.
你的世界正面临着危机  巴里·艾伦
Your world is in danger, Barry Allen.
请听我解释
Please, just let me explain.
我不会伤害你们
I mean you no harm.
你怎么知道我名字
How do you know my name?
我知道你们所有人的名字  凯特琳·斯诺
I know all your names. Caitlin Snow,
西斯科·拉蒙  乔·韦斯特警探
Cisco Ramon, Detective Joe West...
够了
Enough.
现在就解释吧
That part about explaining needs to happen right about now.
这个世界正面临着危机
This world is in danger.
还有别的世界吗
What other worlds are there?
当你在中城制造了奇点
When you created the singularity above Central City,
你也在我们两个世界之间制造了一个缺口
you also created a breach between my world and yours.
你说什么  一个缺口
I'm sorry, a breach?
对  连接两个世界的传送门
Yes, a portal connecting our two earths.
那你的担忧的是什么
And what precisely is your concern?
几天前  你在核电站发现了
A few days ago, you found a dead man named Al Rothstein
阿尔·罗斯坦的尸体
at the nuclear plant.
但又有另一个阿尔·罗斯坦试图杀掉你
But then a different Al Rothstein tried to kill you.
原子粉碎者
Atom Smasher.
那个人是从我的世界来的
That man was from my world.
如果他穿过了缺口
If he got through the breach,
我想还有更多人会来
I suspect there'll be more to follow.
那么  杰伊
Okay, so, Jay,
你是怎么知道这一切的
how exactly do you know all of this?
在我的世界里  我也是个极速者
Where I came from, I was a speedster like you.
他们叫我闪电侠
They called me The Flash.
在我来你们的地球之前
Before I arrived on your earth,
我在跟一个叫极速的人打斗
I was in a fight with a man named Zoom.
极速
Zoom?
我听过这个名字
I've heard that name before.
原子粉碎者  他说极速派他来杀我
Atom Smasher, he said Zoom sent him here to kill me.
那他是谁
Who is this guy?
跟我们一样  也是个极速者
He's a speedster, like you and me.
他速度非常快  可能是最快的
And fast. Maybe the fastest of all.
但他很邪恶
But evil.
他有着死神的脸孔  是无人能挡的恶魔
He is an unstoppable demon with the face of death.
我们在进行一场最激烈的战斗
We were engaged in our fiercest battle ever,
在我的城市里狂奔
racing throughout my city.
但我不够快  没能阻止他
But I wasn't fast enough to stop him.
极速打败了我
Zoom has me beaten.
他正准备杀我
He was about to kill me
突然出现了一道耀眼的强光
when suddenly there was a blinding light
天空裂开了
and the sky split open.
在我们两个世界之间  出现一个缺口
A breach, between my world and yours,
是奇点造成的
caused from the singularity.
它把我吸了进去
It pulled me in...
我不知怎么就到了你们的世界
And I somehow ended up in your world.
没了能力  回不了家
Powerless. Unable to return home.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我的速度不见了
I lost my speed.
原因呢
How?
还不能确定
Not entirely sure.
所以  你来中城已经半年了
So, you've been in Central City for six months.
之前怎么不来找我们
Why haven't you come to see us before?
我在一个陌生的世界  警探
I'm in a foreign world here, Detective.
我不知道你们都是谁
I didn't know who you all were.
我花了这么久才弄清楚的
Took me that long to piece it all together.
所以你才知道我们的名字
So that's how you know our names.
你一直跟踪我们
You've been following us.
我知道这听上去有点疯
Look, I know how this sounds.
另一个地球的存在
The existence of another earth,
你  另一个闪电侠
you, another Flash,
我自己也很震惊
it all came as an unexpected shock to me, too.
我希望能做些什么  让你们相信我
I just wish there was something I could do to convince you.
行
There is.
我们要...对你做些测试
We're gonna... do some tests on you.
看你说的是不是真的
See if you're telling us the truth.
因为如果你撒谎  这个极速
'Cause if you're not, this Zoom,
就不是你唯一的敌人
he's not gonna be your only enemy.
我这是在哪里
Where the hell am I?
你想回家吗
You want to go home?
只要做一件事就行
You only have to do one thing.
什么事
What's that?
杀掉闪电侠
Kill The Flash.
加里克先生
So, Mr. Garrick,
你在自己的世界当了多久的闪电侠
how long have you been The Flash on your world?
还没久到让人叫我先生的程度
Not long enough to call me Mister.
叫我杰伊就好
Please, it's Jay.
杰伊
Jay, of course.
在我的世界  我做闪电侠
On my world, I've been The Flash
做了两年左右
for about two years.
你是怎么获得速度的
And how did you get your speed?
我也不清楚  当时我在实验室
Not really sure. I was at my lab
试着在没有剩余辐射的情况下净化重水
trying to purify heavy water without any residual radiation
突然出现了一道刺眼的光
when there was a blinding light.
我陷入了昏迷  当我醒来
I fell into a coma. When I woke up,
我的速度几乎赶得上光速
I could run almost as fast as the speed of light.
你刚才是说实验室吗
Sorry. Did you say lab?
你也是个科学家吗
Are you a scientist?
我可没有这么高级的实验室
Well, I certainly didn't work at a place like this,
不过我的确是
but, yeah.
我一直都是单干的
I had a respectable solo operation.
兼化学家和物理学家
Part-time chemist, part-time physicist.
还兼超级英雄
Part-time superhero.
不过现在我可以跟超级英雄的日子说再见了
I can forget that superhero part now, though, huh?
这一切真的可能吗
Is any of this possible?
连接另一个世界的缺口  这不可能吧
A breach to another earth? It's not, right?
确实有可能  最近发生的事情说明
The contrary. Just recently,
我们与平行世界交汇
the many-different-worlds theory proposed interaction
这种多重世界理论确实有其道理
with parallel universes was plausible.
如果加里克先生说的是真的
Now, if what Mr. Garrick's saying is true,
这个理论早就被证实了
that theory's been proven sooner than we all thought.
我觉得这一点也不合理
It doesn't add up.
我说实话吧
I'm gonna be honest here,
你们刚才说的我根本没听懂
I don't understand what the hell any of you are talking about.
杰伊要表达的是
So, Jay is saying he's from,
他来自一个镜像世界
like, a mirror-world.
也可以说是平行宇宙
Or a parallel universe
这个世界跟我们的世界非常相似
that's very, very similar to ours.
说这是多元宇宙应该更恰当
Multiverse would be a more apt description.
-还是不懂  -无知是福啊
- No, not helping. - Bless your heart.
我来解释吧
Okay, let's see if this helps.
这是我们的地球
This is our earth.
就叫它地球一
Let's call it Earth-1.
这第二个地球  我们可以叫它
And this second earth, let's call it
地球二
Earth-2.
杰伊就是来自地球二
This is where Jay claims to be from.
其它的地球  地球三  四  五
And these other earths, three, four, five,
还有无穷的其它地球  它们都跟我们的类似
to infinity, all of them, are nearly identical to ours.
这些世界都同时存在
And they all exist at the same time,
于是给予了我们无穷的存在
giving us endless alternatives to what we have here.
比如说地球二上乔·韦斯特的二重身
For example, the Joe West on Earth-2, your doppelganger,
也许他不是个警探
he might not be a detective.
他可能是一名得到诺奖的物理学家
He could be a Nobel Prize-winning physicist.
在这里  巴里·艾伦是闪电侠
And you, the Barry Allen here is The Flash,
在另一个地球  也许他就是个电工
but over there, he could be an electrician.
其它地球的人
So, I'm assuming that the people on all these other earths
应该也要挣钱付账单之类的吧
work to make money to pay bills and such.
-应该是的  -看来我们还是有共同点的
- I would imagine. - So we got that in common.
我要回警察局了
I'm heading back to the station.
等这一切说得通了再联系我
Call me when this makes a little bit more sense.
我要花点时间接受这个时空旅行理论
I'm still trying to wrap my head around this whole idea of time travel.
还有一个问题
There is one problem that remains.
如果加里克先生说的都是真的
If Mr. Garrick is telling the truth,
那么在中城某处
there is a breach
有一个缺口  我们得找到缺口
somewhere in Central City that we need to find
把它关上  以绝后患
and close for good.
可是怎么样才能找到呢
Yeah, but how do we find it?
我们都不知道从哪开始
We don't even know what to look for.
我们大家凑在一起
Well, I-I suggest we put our heads together
想一个办法出来
and come up with a solution.
当然  不是所有人一起了
Not literally, of course.
那段日子不复存在
Those days are over.
-有什么结果吗  -杰伊的心率非常低
- What'd you find? - Well, Jay's heart rate is extraordinarily low.
他也的确有再生能力
And he does have regenerative capabilities.
除此之外  我没有发现其它证据
Other than that, I'm not seeing any evidence
证明他体内有超速能力
of the Speed Force in his system.
我们甚至无法证明他是极速者
We don't even have proof that he's a speedster,
就跟无法证明另一个地球存在一样
much less from another earth?
也不一定
Not necessarily.
为什么这么说
What does that mean?
杰伊没发现
Well, Jay doesn't know this,
不过当时我不仅测量了他的心率
but while I was testing his heart rate,
血压  运动反应
blood pressure, and motor responses,
我还监测了谈话时他的自主反应
I also measured his autonomic reactions while we were talking.
你还给他测谎了啊
You gave him a lie detector test?
他通过了测谎
And he passed it.
万一他不是好人
What if he's not a good guy,
他只想找出我们的弱点呢
and he just wants to find our weaknesses?
继续进行测试  看看能否找到别的信息
Keep running tests. See what else you can find out.
韦斯特警探
Detective West, sir.
你好  请问你是
Yes, Officer...?
斯皮沃特  帕蒂·斯皮沃特
Spivot. Patty Spivot.
辛格队长说了
Captain Singh mentioned
你的反超能力者特别行动小组可能还要人
there may be positions available on your anti-meta-human task force.
大家都退出了  没有所谓的小组了
Yeah, everybody quit. There is no task force anymore.
我认识一个想要加入的人
Well, I know someone who's interested in being on it.
我
Me.
你知道
You do realize that
超能力者是有超能力的  对吧
meta-humans have super powers, right?
就算他们没有超能力
And even if they didn't,
你也不适合加入这个小组
you wouldn't be a good fit for the team.
因为我是女人吗
Because I'm a woman?
我不是这个意思
I didn't mean to imply that.
那就好  因为我知道这工作会有多难
Good, because I know how difficult this job would be,
但是我觉得我是个不错的候选人
but I think I'm an excellent candidate.
我在哈德森学院主攻生物  化学和物理
I triple-majored at Hudson in biology, chemistry, and physics.
我的身体处于最佳状态
I'm in prime physical condition.
并且在我同级中  我的枪法最好
And I rated top of my class in marksmanship.
你的同级
Your class?
你连级别肩章都没拿到呢
You don't even have your stripes yet.
马上就有了  已经干了七个月了  长官
Soon. Been on the job seven months, sir.
你知道我之前搭档的下场吗
Are you aware of what happened to my previous partner?
斯旺警探  知道
Detective Thawne, yes.
我知道他死了  而在他之前那任
I know that he died and the one before him,
弗雷德·夏尔  也死了
Fred Chyre, died, too,
但再之前那位没有死
but the one before that's not dead,
只是调离了
just transferred.
我肯定跟你无关
I'm sure it had nothing to do with you.
听着  警官...
Listen, Officer...
斯皮沃特  帕蒂·斯皮沃特
Spivot, Patty Spivot.
对  斯皮沃特  回答是不行
Yes, Spivot, the answer's no.
只要给我一个机会  长官
All I'm asking for is a shot, sir.
求你了  我要的只是一次面试
Please, just an interview.
你已经面试完了
You just had the interview.
你不被录取
Didn't get the job.
我希望你能明白这些是必须的
I hope you understand why we have to do this.
我明白  孩子
I get it, kid.
你在做你认为你该做的
You're doing what you think you have to.
但很快你会明白  这...
But you'll all realize soon enough that this,
这些测试  都是没必要的
the tests, it's unnecessary.
我想要帮助你  巴里  不是伤害你
I want to help you, Barry, not harm you.
你不是第一个对我说这种话的人
You're not the first person that's said that to me.
如果你告诉我关于极速的事情是真的
If what you told me about Zoom is true,
他派了罗斯坦来杀你
that he sent Rothstein here to kill you,
那就不应该把我锁在这里
instead of locking me up in here,
你应该开始听听建议
you better start listening.
因为如果极速真的是幕后黑手
Because if Zoom is involved,
你就需要不止我一个人的帮助
you are gonna need a lot more than just me at your side
才能活下去了
to stay alive.
巴里  滨水区那里有场大火
Barry, there's a fire at the Waterfront.
消防部门已经赶去了
Fire department's on route.
我马上就去
I'm on my way.
小心点
Be careful.
那是闪电侠
That was The Flash.
还真是场大火
That was a big fire.
扑灭了  西斯科
It's out, Cisco.
收到  等会见
Copy that, see you in a bit.
我还以为会更难对付一点呢
I thought it would be harder than this.
巴里
Barry?
喂  还在吗
Hello? Are you there?
-什么情况  -我不知道
- What was that? - I don't know.
我们得去查出来
We need to find out.
巴仔
Bar.
咱们要对付的是什么
What are we dealing with here?
肯定是超能力者
Well, definitely a meta-human.
在打斗期间我仔细地观察了下他
Had a pretty solid look at him between punches.
他好像是沙子组成的
And he was, like, made of sand.
沙子
Sand?
这些墙太潮湿了  弄不到指纹
Okay. These walls are too porous to pull any prints.
船上也弄不到
I can't even get one off the boat,
不过看看这个
but check this out.
到处都有汽油燃烧痕迹
There's gasoline burns everywhere.
没有洒水
Water didn't go off.
消防喷洒坏掉了
Sprinklers weren't working.
这是蓄意纵火
This was arson.
打扰一下  巴里·艾伦
Excuse me? Barry Allen?
是的
Yeah.
连续两天  警官  真是巧啊
Two days in a row, Officer. What a coincidence.
或是天命  如果你相信命运或是定数的话
Or kismet, if you believe in destiny or fate.
我是帕蒂  帕蒂·斯皮沃特
I'm Patty. Patty Spivot.
真高兴能见到你
I'm really excited to meet you.
我是你的大粉丝
I'm a huge fan.
什么
Excuse me?
你的法医鉴定报告  我有时候会看
Your forensic reports. I-I read them sometimes.
我瞎说什么呢  天天看
Who am I kidding? All the time.
我全部都看过
I've actually read them all.
我想我都没有全看过
Wow, I don't think that I've read them all.
它们总是写的很详细
They're always so detailed.
你知道  它们就像是在说
You know, they really paint a picture
似乎你当时就在场
like you were somehow actually there
看着某个人被残忍地杀害了
when somebody was being brutally murdered.
谢谢
Thank you.
不管怎样  我找到了些线索
Uh, anyhow, I-I found, uh, something.
我觉得我找到了些线索  都是理论而已
Well, I think I found something. It's just a theory,
但是我想给你看看
but I would like to show you.
好啊
Great.
那么  这里是最初的起火点
So, this right here is the point of origin of the fire.
看看这个
And look.
我不知道市面上有任何喷砂器
I don't know a sandblaster on the market
能做出这么精准的切割
that can make a cut that precise,
所以我觉得可能是超能力者干的
so I think a meta-human may have done this.
给  帮你提取了一些样本
Here. Took a sample for you.
而且我在管道后边
Uh, there's also some fingerprints
还找到了一些指纹
on the back of the pipe.
你应该去做犯罪现场调查
You should have gone into CSI work.
我爱科学  但是大场面都是在这里
I love the science, but out here's where all the action is.
是不是这样  韦斯特警探
Isn't that right, Detective West?
回答依然是不行  警官...
The answer's still no, Officer S...
-斯皮沃特  -斯皮沃特
- Spivot. - Spivot.
刚才那是怎么回事
What was that about?
我想加入反超能力者特别行动小组
I'm trying to join the anti-meta-human task force.
可是你也听到他怎么说了
But you heard him.
对了  他就像是你父亲  对吧
Hey, he's kinda like your dad, right?
有什么建议能让他改变想法吗
So, do you have any advice on how I can crack his no-code?
我十一岁的时候就开始尝试了
Yeah, I've been trying to pick that lock since I was 11.
所以等你找到了门路  告诉我好吗
So, if you figure it out, how about you let me know?
-可以  -好的
- Deal. - All right.
很高兴见到你  巴里
It was nice to meet you, Barry.
我也是
Yeah, you too.
他的血压很低  心率也很低
His blood pressure is low, his heart rate is low,
但是他的含氧量很高
his oxygen levels are impressive.
是的  不过跟巴里比起来不算什么
Yeah, but nothing compared to Barry's.
是的  不过他绝对属于身体很强壮的类型
No, but he's certainly in the physical specimen range.
你这是话中有话
In more ways than one.
我没注意到那方面
Oh, I wasn't paying attention.
今天就到这  杰伊
That's enough for today, Jay.
谢谢
Thank you.
在犯罪现场发现的
Found it at the crime scene.
肯定是从袭击我的那个超能力者身上掉下来的
I mean, it's gotta be from the meta-human that attacked me.
这是什么东西  沙子吗
What is this stuff? Sand?
不是沙子
It's not sand.
是人体细胞  它的肌球蛋白II
It's human cells whose myosin II protein
已经与细胞外围融合了
have migrated to the cell's periphery.
杰伊也是个科学牛人
Jay's a fellow science nerd.
这些细胞具有重新排列和变坚固的能力
Those cells have the ability to rearrange and harden,
使他们看上去像沙子
giving them the appearance of sand.
你是怎么知道的
And how do you know this?
它们属于一个超能力者
They belong to a meta-human
我之前跟他打过交道  名字叫沙妖
I've fought before named Sand Demon.
我知道你是新来的
I know you're new here,
所以我就跟你直说了
so I'm just gonna break it down for you.
给坏人起名这件事
The whole naming the bad guys thing,
是我负责的  可是你知道吗
that's my jam. But you know what?
这次就用你的  因为我挺喜欢这个名字的
I'm gonna let you have that one 'cause I actually kinda like it.
我对这个挺满意
I'm not mad at that one.
那是巴里的运动衫吗
Is that Barry's sweatshirt?
抱歉  我们只能找到这一件  所以
Oh, sorry. It was all we could find, so...
我只是觉得你穿着有点小
I was gonna say, 'cause it looks a lot smaller on you, right?
我得研究一下这玩意
I gotta do this thing.
沙妖是谁
So, who is this Sand Demon?
我不知道他的名字
I don't know his name,
可是我知道该怎么阻止他
but I know how to stop him.
其实
You know what?
我想我们自己就行了
I think we'll be fine on our own.
巴里  我不知道我还能做什么
Look, Barry, I don't know what else I can do
才能证明我跟你们是一伙的
to prove to you I'm on your side.
我被刺过  被扎过
I've been poked, prodded.
甚至还做了全身扫瞄
I even subjected myself to a full body scan.
我做得很全面
I was being thorough.
沙妖来自我的世界
Sand Demon's from my world.
让我来教你怎么阻止他
Let me teach you how to stop him.
我不需要你教我什么  杰伊
Yeah, I don't need you to teach me anything, Jay.
极速之前派了罗斯坦来杀你
Zoom sent Rothstein here to kill you.
他派沙妖来一定也是做同样的事
He must have sent Sand Demon here to do the same thing.
你还不明白吗  跟闪电侠亲近的人
Don't you get it? Anyone close to the Flash,
所有的人  都有很大的危险
all of you, are in a lot of danger.
好吧
All right.
如果你很厉害的话
If you're so good,
你早就抓住他了
you would have caught him already.
还是让杰伊回他的牢房吧
Let's get Jay back to his cell.
帅哥
Hey, beautiful mind,
我觉得你该休息一下了
I think you need to take a breather.
经过一些漫长的计算后
After some lengthy calculations,
我相信我已经发现了
I believe I have discovered the key
证明所谓的缺口理论的关键
to proving the proposed breach theory.
奇异物质
Exotic matter.
你是指
You mean, like,
跨维能源
transdimensional energy?
没错  奇异物质
Precisely. Exotic matter,
跨维能源在理论上能够
transdimensional energy will theoretically leak
从一个宇宙泄露到另外一个
from one universe into another.
如果加里克先生所说的缺口是真的
Now, if this breach Mr. Garrick's talking about is real,
如果我们宇宙中真有一个洞通往他的地球
if there is indeed a hole in our universe which leads to his earth...
我们可以稍作调整
We can make some adjustments
向尖端科研实验室的卫星
and upload an electrophotography program
上传电子摄影术程序  这样就能
to the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite and essentially photograph
拍摄到奇异物质泄露
the exotic matter leak.
这样我们就能知道缺口的位置了
Thereby giving us the locale of said breach.
上次我见到那个装备  还是在制造间里
Last time I saw the kit, it was in the fabrication room.
我马上回来
I shall return.
这老顽童
Getting gooseys.
好了
All right.
看看你是由什么构成的
Let's see what you're made of.
太多了
That's too much.
巴里
Barry?
我还以为会更难对付一点呢
I thought it'd be harder than this.
我这是怎么了
What's happening to me?
我找到那个超能力者了
I found our meta.
他的名字叫艾迪·斯利克
His name is Eddie Slick.
我们通过指纹找到了他的地址
We tracked those prints to his address.
好的  你在哪  我去找你
All right, where are you? I'll meet you there.
来不及了  他发现我了
Too late. He made me.
什么  乔
What? Joe?
现在我能加入你的特别行动小组了吗
So, can I be on your task force?
看着眼熟吗
That look familiar?
这样呢
How about now?
-看起来像什么  -大火
- What's it look like? - A fire.
答对了  真聪明
There you go, genius.
这是你昨晚在三号仓库放的火
It's the fire you started in the third ward last night.
我昨晚没在那放火
Man, I didn't start no fire there last night.
怎么  你不在城里吗
What? Were you out of town?
你的猫生病了
Your cat get sick?
让我猜猜
Well, let me guess.
你不再纵火了是吧
You don't start fires anymore.
你有前科
You been rehabilitated.
没错  我有前科又怎么了
Yeah, I done it before. So what?
这次不是我干的
I didn't do this one.
我放火一般都用很难被查到的材料
I always start a fire with something that's hard to trace.
像是丙酮什么的
You know, like acetone or something.
没准你不再需要催化剂了
Or maybe you don't need to use accelerants anymore.
铁山监狱就是为你们这种人设计的
Iron Heights can hold people like you now.
这一点你明白吧
You know that, right?
你认为我是那种超能力怪胎吗
You think I'm one of those meta-human freaks?
我要有那种能力  你不觉得我早就会
If I had powers, you don't think I would have used them
用它来摆脱你们了吗
to get away from you?
2013年十二月  你在什么地方
December, 2013. Where were you?
-怎么了  -回答我的问题
- Why? - Answer the damn question.
-那时候你在哪儿  -黑门监狱
- Where were you? - Blackgate Penitentiary.
不相信的话  去查查就知道了
You don't believe me. Check your records.
吉米  我需要你帮我确认件事
Jimmy, I need you to confirm something for me.
乔跟我说了你的壮举
So, Joe told me what you did.
不错哦
I'm impressed.
没有了  我只是
No, all I did was, you know,
追查了管道上的另外一个指纹
run the other print from the electrical pipe,
然后追踪到了斯利克
then track Slick down from there.
就是这么简单
That's all.
是啊
Yeah.
和乔那里进展的怎么样
How's it going with Joe?
有没有想到办法改变他的想法
You any closer to cracking his no-code?
简直不敢相信
Are you kidding me?
他就像斯芬克斯的谜题一样
He's like the permission Sphinx.
一种占卜玩具，问问题后可以获得随机的回答
或是个魔术八球  但只有一个回答
Or like a magic eight ball with just one answer.
或者说是
Or like, you know,
保护圣杯的守桥人
the Bridgekeeper protecting the Holy Grail.
-你在追寻什么  -加入你们的特遣部队
- What is your quest? - Oh, to join your task force.
答错了
No.
也许我能帮你说点好话
Well, maybe I can put in a good word for you.
那真是太令我感激了  巴里
That would mean a lot to me, Barry.
他找的是我
He needs me.
粒子加速器爆炸那晚
Okay, so, Slick wasn't in Central City
斯利克不在中城
the night the particle accelerator exploded.
他在说谎
He's lying.
他是个邋遢鬼  还是纵火犯
He's a dirt bag, and an arsonist,
但这件事他没说谎
but he's not lying about this.
他不是个超能力者 巴里
He's not a meta, Barry.
斯利克就是那个袭击我的人
Slick is the guy who jumped me.
你觉得有没有可能
Do you think it's possible
那里的斯利克有个...
that the Slick in there has a--
二重身吗  我也不知道
A doppelganger? I don't know.
昨天  突如其来的一段来自星城义警
Yesterday's surprise broadcast from a Star City vigilante
星城守护者
昨天  突如其来的一段来自星城义警
Yesterday's surprise broadcast from a Star City vigilante
自称绿箭侠之人的公共广播
星城守护者
who is calling himself the Green Arrow
自称绿箭侠之人的公共广播
引起了其支持者...
has spawned a massive outcry...
有意思
和反对者的强烈抗议 [背景对白]
Catchy.
我讨厌那些用颜色起名字的人
和反对者的强烈抗议 [背景对白]
I hate it when they put a color in their name.
我讨厌那些用颜色起名字的人
你给我们的样本
The sample you gave us?
不是沙子
Not sand.
绝对是人类细胞
Definitely human cells.
我知道  不是他  我懂
Yeah, I know. It's not him, I get it.
不得不说  但"地球二"这个推论
I hate to say it, but I think this Earth-2 theory
-越来越站得住脚了  -真的吗
- is starting to make sense. - For real?
你认为杰伊在沙妖这件事上说谎了吗
What, you think Jay is lying about the Sand Demon?
我也不知道  这就是我想说的
I don't know. That's my point.
我不会轻信一个擅自闯入这里
But I'm not gonna just believe some guy that walks in here
然后说了一些可能是真事的人
and says a few things that sort of check out.
可能  极速的事他就没说错
Sort of? He was--he was right about Zoom.
我们根本就不了解极速
We don't even know anything about Zoom.
极速是什么  真的存在吗
What is Zoom? Is Zoom even real?
就目前的情况来看  它就是那么个
Right now, that's just, you know, a story
围坐在篝火前讲的故事
around a campfire.
我是说  你找到缺口了吗
I mean, have you discovered a breach yet?
还没  但现在我们知道怎么找了
Not yet, but we know how to now.
你有找到哪怕一点能证明杰伊是个极速者吗
Have you found one thing to suggest that Jay is a speedster?
他体内真的有神速力吗
Is the Speed Force even in his system?
目前看起来没有
It doesn't appear to be, no.
看到没
See?
我们是科学家
We are scientists.
你是名记者
You are a journalist.
我们试验  证明  然后报道  这才是我们该做的
We test, we prove, we report. That's what we do.
只不过现在  这里的人除了我
Except right now, nobody here wants to do any of that
都没想这么做
except me.
能让我俩单独聊聊么
Can we have the room for a minute?
你这是怎么了
What has happened to you?
你是说  我
Are you--me?
就是你
Yes, you.
和我一起长大的你
The you that I grew up with.
跟我最要好的那个你
The you that is my best friend.
成为闪电侠的那个你
The you that became The Flash.
我很久都没见到那个时候的你了
I haven't seen that you in a very long time.
很多东西变了  爱瑞丝
A lot's changed, Iris.
没错  确实是变了
Yeah, it sure has.
你学会了如何不信任别人
You have learned how to not trust people.
你不喜欢杰伊哪里
What is it about Jay that you don't like?
我也说不准
I don't know.
是他总让你想起哈里森·威尔斯
It's because he reminds you of Harrison Wells.
我那么信任他
I trusted that man.
长久以来  我们都信任他
For months. We all did.
但你猜怎么的
And you know what?
艾迪死了
Eddie is dead.
罗尼死了
Ronnie is dead.
还有这座城市里面的很多人
And a whole lot of other people in this city,
也因为信任他而死掉了
they are dead because we trusted him.
我不会让我们再犯同样的错误
I'm not gonna let us make that mistake again.
巴里
Barry,
不是所有人都是哈里森·威尔斯
not everyone is Harrison Wells.
再说了  你就是因为相信他人才打败了他
Besides, you defeated him because you trusted in people.
因为你相信他们
Because you believed in them.
在这里的这个团队
This team that you have here,
他们会追随着你
they will follow your lead.
他们会照你说的做
They'll do what you say.
但是如果他们认为你不信任他们
But if they think that you don't believe in them,
过不了多久他们也就不信任你了
it won't be long before they don't believe in you.
赶紧离开
Get to walking.
我不想再在这里见到你那张蠢脸
I don't want to see your ugly mug around here again.
撒哟娜拉
Sayonara.
我们没有合理依据
We didn't have probable cause.
我懂的
I get it.
有件事你需要知道
One thing you should know
和这些超能力者打交道
about dealing with these meta-humans,
事情永远不会像是他们看起来的那样
nothing is ever as it seems.
说到这个
Speaking of which,
你是这里唯一一个
you're the only person here
想要加入我的特别行动小组的人
who wants to be on my task force.
你能告诉我你为什么要这么执着吗
You want to tell me why you're so hell-bent on being on it?
你能告诉我为什么你这么执着的拒绝我吗
You want to tell me why you're so hell-bent I'm not?
我难道不是刚告诉过你
Didn't I just tell you
我不想再在这里看到你这张蠢脸了吗
I didn't want to see your ugly mug around here again?
但你不得不看  韦斯特警探
Well, you're gonna have to, Detective West.
这样我就能干掉闪电侠了
So I can get to the Flash.
我喜欢你  你来当诱饵...
I like you. You'll do the trick...
刚刚好
just fine.
你终于恢复理智了吗
Finally come to your senses?
沙妖绑架了一名警察
Sand Demon kidnapped a police officer.
一个我认识的女人
A woman that I know.
你需要我的帮助吗
And you need my help?
我需要你帮我们一起救她
I need you to help us save her.
以免事态变得更严重
Before something happens.
看来你没得选必须要信任我了  小子
I guess you're gonna have to trust me now, huh, kid?
我们需要找出任何湿度较大的建筑
We're looking for any structures that promote humidity.
温室  种植大棚  那一类的建筑
Greenhouses, grow rooms, anything of the sort.
如果他开始出现脱水状态的话
His body will literally start to fall apart
他的身体就会崩溃
if he becomes dehydrated.
-就像干掉的沙子  -没错
- Like dry sand. - Exactly.
沙妖总是从两方面展开进攻
Sand Demon always attacks on two fronts.
他会声东击西
He creates a diversion,
等你分神之后  就发动袭击
then strikes when you're distracted.
好的  我们要做什么
Okay, then what do we do?
我们利用你的速度找到他
We use your speed to get to him
在他进行声东击西之前
before the distraction can happen.
杰伊  我要怎么阻止一个
Jay, how do I stop somebody
可以从我指缝里面溜走的人
who can slip through my fingers?
利用我一直无法做到的方法
The way I was never able to.
利用闪电
With lightning.
你这是要叫来宙斯吗
Yo, are you about to pull a Zeus right now?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
巴里将要用力投掷出
Barry's gonna hurl lightning
他奔跑时产生的能量闪电
from the energy he creates when he runs.
因为闪电加上沙子就等于
Because lightning plus sand equals
玻璃
Glass.
是时候学个新技能了  孩子
Time to learn something new, kid.
好吧
All right.
稍等一下
Give me a sec.
你还好吗
Hey, are you good?
是辛格
That was Singh.
中城警局还是没能有任何发现
CCPD still hasn't found anything yet.
讽刺的是  一开始我就不希望帕蒂
Irony is, I didn't want Patty to have anything to do with
和这该死的特别行动小组有什么关系
the damn task force in the first place.
她被劫走都是因为我
And she gets taken because of me.
不不  这不是你的错  好吗
No, no, no, this isn't your fault, all right?
很难不那样想
It's hard not to think that.
听着  我们会找到帕蒂的  好吗
Well, look, we're gonna find Patty, all right?
无论需要什么代价
Whatever it takes.
闪电侠要会来治你的  知道吗
Flash is coming for you, you know?
当然  我很肯定他会来
Yes, I'm sure he is.
你打不过他的
You can't beat him.
不管你有什么能力
I don't care what powers you have.
那可不一定
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
这就是你建造那个冲击炸弹的原因吗
Is that why you need to build that concussive bomb?
是的  我知道那是什么
Yeah, I know what it is.
我是警察  我之前见过
I'm a cop. I've seen one before.
这个杀不死闪电侠
This isn't gonna kill the Flash.
我会杀死他
I am.
这个会杀了你
This...is gonna kill you.
你知道你只是运气好  对吧
You know you got lucky, right?
你觉得你是被选中之人
You think you were chosen.
我们其余的人什么都不是
The rest of us don't mean anything.
但那不是真的
But it's not true.
你只是恰好在那个时间出现在合适的地方而已
You were just at the right place at the right time.
获得这些能力没有改变你的本性
Getting those powers didn't change who you are.
它们只突显了你人格中最糟的部分
They only highlighted the worst parts of who you already were.
也许你是对的
Maybe you're right.
也许不对
Maybe not.
不管怎样  你和闪电侠马上要见证
Either way, you and the Flash are about to find out
这些最糟的部分了
what those worst parts are.
不匹配
我搜寻了中城所有闲置建筑
I've searched all the vacant buildings in Central City
没有一个和我们要找的描述相符
and none of them fit the description that we need.
我检查了输电网络图是否有飙升
And I've looked at any draw upticks on the electrical grid.
恐怕没什么异常
Nothing out of the norm, I'm afraid.
我们要不惜一切代价
We gotta do whatever it takes.
我马上回来
I'll be back.
好了  加把劲
Okay, come on.
闪电侠要来找你  知道吗
Flash is coming for you, you know?
是的  我知道他会来
Yes, I'm sure he is.
你无法打败他
You can't beat him.
无论你的能力是什么
I don't care what powers you have.
这我可说不太准了
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
不
Oh, no.
拉蒙先生
Mr. Ramon?
你在这下面做什么呢
What are you doing down here?
我知道帕蒂在哪了
I figured out where Patty is.
你是怎么办到的
And how exactly did you do that?
凭直觉
Just a hunch.
我们得告诉巴里
We gotta tell Barry.
再来
Again.
我已经持续一个小时了
I've been doing this for an hour.
没什么作用
It's not working.
因为你急于求成
It's because you're trying to rush it.
这一次需要你慢下来
This is the one time you need to slow down.
让能量贯穿全身
Let the energy pass over you,
然后把它指引到你想要的地方
then simply direct it to where you want it to go.
好了  杰伊
All right, Jay...
我不知道能否及时学会这个
I don't know if I'm gonna get this in time.
你会学会的  我相信你
You'll get it. I believe in you.
上一个这样教我的人
The last person that helped me like this
是我敬仰的人
was a man that I looked up to.
崇拜的
Idolized.
他教会了我如何更快  如何更强
He taught me how to get faster, how to get stronger,
如何用我的能力去救人
how to use my powers to save people.
也是这个人谋杀了我母亲
That same man murdered my mother.
这很不幸
It's a tough break,
但我不是他
but I'm not him.
知道
Yeah.
我知道他们在哪了
I know where they are!
废弃的香车叶草种植屋
The abandoned Woodruff grow house.
斯利克就把帕蒂关在那
That's where Slick's keeping Patty.
伙计  好样的
Dude, great job.
而且我想到了  如果我是沙妖
And I was thinking, if I were Sand Demon
我要攻击两个疾驰的极速者的话
and I were attacking a speedster on two fronts,
我大概会先让你们减速
I would probably want to slow you down,
比如用震荡爆弹或类似的东西
like, by using a concussive bomb or something like that.
这想法不错
That's a good thought.
他从前对我用过这个
He's actually used one on me before.
他能吸收爆炸冲击  不会受其影响
His body absorbs the blast so it doesn't affect him.
好吧  孩子  得想个办法了
Well, kid, gonna have to think of something.
不如这样
You know what?
去分散斯利克的注意力如何
What if we give Slick a diversion?
他认识你  对吧
He knows you, right?
你说你和他对抗过
You said you went up against him.
对  可是巴里  我没有速度了
Yeah, but, Barry, I don't have my speed.
他并不知道
He doesn't know that.
你的战衣还在吗
You got your suit?
当然了  除了我的头盔
Sure. Well, except my helmet.
-什么头盔  -银壶头盔吗
- Helmet? - Silver kettle helmet?
有金色翅膀的
Gold wings?
别告诉我你们找到它了
Don't tell me you guys found it.
我还以为再也见不到它了
Never thought I'd see that again.
这是我爸爸的
It was my father's,
在美洲战争时留下的
from the War of the Americas.
你刚说的是美洲战争吗
Did you just say War of the Americas?
我希望你只告诉我们丢了头盔
I wish you would have just told us you lost your helmet.
也不会让我们产生困扰了
Would have saved us all a headache.
确定想这样做吗  闪电侠
Well, sure you want to do this, Flash?
是的
Yeah.
让我看看你的厉害  闪电侠
Let's go see what you're made of...Flash.
我接进监控信号了
I'm in the security feed.
快去  巴里
Go, Barry!
是你吗  闪电侠
Is that you, Flash?
你找到这里来了
Found your way here.
我走了相当远
I came quite a distance.
我以为你死了
I thought you were dead.
你错了
You were wrong.
和往常一样
Like usual.
放了那个女孩
Let the girl go.
尽管来  但你若碰她一下
Have at it. But you touch her,
她就会爆炸
she goes boom.
即使你的速度也救不了她
And I think even you aren't fast enough to save her.
在这个世界你慢了不少啊  闪电侠
Quite a bit slower on this Earth, aren't you, Flash?
你没有速度了  是不是
You don't have your speed, do you?
斯利克分神了  上  巴里
Slick's distracted. Go, Barry.
-杰伊  -巴里
- Jay! - Barry!
帕蒂还活着
Patty's alive.
真是我的幸运日
Must be my lucky day.
极速派我来杀你
Zoom sent me here to kill you.
我必须把两个时空里的闪电侠都干掉
Now I get to kill The Flash from two worlds
才能回家
before I go home.
杰伊要窒息了
He's choking Jay.
巴里  赶快想办法
Barry, you gotta do something now.
来吧
Come on!
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
Yeah. I'm okay.
干得好  孩子
Nice shot, kid.
闪电侠
Flash?
-来了  -来了
- Coming. - Coming.
你很擅长包扎
You're pretty good at this.
去年我经过了大量的练习
I've had a lot of practice over the last year.
你今天真的很勇敢
It was really courageous doing what you did today,
赤手空拳面对沙妖
standing up to the Sand Demon without any powers.
全都靠巴里
Barry did all the work.
我只是站在那  挨了几拳
I just stood there and took a few punches.
不止几拳
It was more than a few.
比我想像的要艰难
This is a lot harder than I thought.
这么以来  失去已经成为了
Losing something that was such a big part
造就我的重要部分
of who I was for so long.
我也失去了一些东西
I lost something that was a part of me, too.
很艰难
It's hard,
但每天都会变得容易一点
but it gets easier every day.
只是得找个新的生活方式
You just have to find a new way to live.
不同的人生
Just because it's a different life
并不代表会是最糟的
it doesn't mean it's a worse one.
无论是否能高速移动
And, speed or no speed,
在我看来  你今天依然是个英雄
in my book you were still a hero today.
只是抱歉
I'm just sorry
我们没能早点意识到这点
we didn't all realize it a little bit sooner.
尤其是我
Especially me.
让你们俩极速者好好聊聊吧
I'll leave you two speedsters alone.
听说大家都叫你红色极速者
So, I hear they call you the Scarlet Speedster?
是的
Yeah.
-你呢  -红色彗星
- What about you? - Crimson Comet?
押韵和昵称如何
What is it with alliteration and nicknames?
听着  杰伊
Hey, look, Jay...
谢谢你所有的帮忙
so, thank you for all your help.
并且一直对我如此耐心
And for being so patient with me.
不客气  孩子  你学得很快
Nah, anytime, kid. You're a quick study.
花了我不少时间才学会如何抛掷闪电
Took me a lot longer to learn how to toss lightning,
相信我
believe me.
看来我有个好老师
Then I suppose I had the right teacher.
要打倒极速就没这么容易了
It's going to be a lot harder to take down Zoom.
他是什么人
Who is this guy?
没人知道
No one knows.
他在我获得超能力的时候出现
He showed up around the same time as when I got my powers.
在我的世界里  他杀了很多人
Killed a lot of people in my world.
两年来我都在追踪他
I spent about two years tracking him down.
但是他太聪明  速度太快
But he was too smart, too quick.
他总是比我先行一步
He's always one step ahead.
你真认为他只是叫这些人来杀我吗
You really think he's just bringing these guys here to kill me?
极速一心想要消灭我
Zoom is obsessed with destroying me.
-现在他想消灭你  -是的
- Now he wants to destroy you. - Yeah.
他要做最厉害的
He needs to be the best.
并且会不惜一切代价
And he will do whatever it takes
来确保他是唯一的极速
to ensure he's the only speedster.
在所有的世界里
In any world.
中城警局
-斯皮沃特警官  -警探
- Officer Spivot? - Detective.
你应该在家休息
You're supposed to be home resting.
我真的没事  长官
I'm okay, sir, really.
很抱歉因为我  让你卷入了
Look, I'm sorry you got mixed up in all this mess
这些混乱中
because of me.
不是你的错
It's not your fault.
你真的认为自己有条件
Do you really think you have what it takes
加入我的特别小组
to be part of my task force?
我知道我有  长官
I know it, sir.
我总是会检查我所考量的
Well, I always check the jacket of anyone
每一个人的底细
I'm considering for it.
我调查过你
In my research on you,
发现我们都认识同一个人
I found out we got a mutual acquaintance.
马克·马登
Mark Mardon.
我要你跟我说实话
I need you to be honest with me here.
你为什么要这么做
Why do you want to do this?
因为马克·马登杀了我爸爸
Mark Mardon killed my dad.
以前他在切斯特菲尔德有家小鞋店
He had a little shoe shop down on Chesterfield.
店里只收现金
It was a cash business.
有一天  他去费尔菲尔德银行
One night he went to Fairfield Bank
把每周的现金存进去
to make his weekly deposit,
结果马登兄弟来了
and the Mardon brothers showed up.
在他排队的时候
While he was waiting in line,
马克为了几百块一枪打死了我爸爸
Mark shot my dad in the face for a few hundred dollars.
几个月后  马克兄弟获得超能力
Then a few months later, Mark and his brother got powers.
两名杀人凶手获得了超能力
Two murderers got superpowers.
这就是我来的原因  长官
So that's why I'm here, Sir.
所以我不顾一切地要加入你的特别小组
That's why I'm so hell-bent on being on your task force.
因为坏人逍遥法外
'Cause there's some bad people out there
他们为所欲为
and they can do anything.
我也许没有超能力
And I may not have powers,
但我想要阻止他们
but I want to stop them.
你是我唯一知道想要抓住这些坏人的人
You're the only person I know who wants to do that, too.
周一早上八点
Monday, 8:00 A.M.
别迟到
Don't be late.
什么别迟到
Late for what?
加入特别小组  警探
The task force, Detective.
约瑟夫
Joseph.
好久不见
Been a long time.
Yeah, it has.
你来这里干什么
Why are you here?
你不接我的电话
Because you didn't return my calls.
我想见你
And I wanted to see you.
还有我们的女儿
And our daughter.
电子图像有何进展
Any progress with the electrophotography?
中城的卫星图像还在组合中
The satellite picture of the city's still rendering.
我们边等边聊
While we wait,
可以告诉我你怎么了吗
care to tell me what's going on with you?
怎么了  没事啊
What? Nothing.
一天料中两件事
Two hunches in one day.
知道斯利克的所在
Slick's locale,
知道他用冲击炸弹
and that he'd be using a concussive bomb
阻碍巴里
to thwart Barry.
你知道发生这类事件的概率吗
Do I need to inform you of the odds of such a prediction?
我出状况了
Something's happening to me.
我可以预见未来
I'm starting to perceive things.
可怕的未来
Horrible things.
从威尔斯在另一个时间线杀死我开始
It started after Wells killed me in the other timeline.
在原子粉碎者袭击闪电侠之日
It came back when Atom Smasher attacked on Flash Day,
还有沙妖出现时发生
and then again when Sand Demon showed up.
我感受到一股震波
I get a vibe,
然后看见已发生的情景
and then a vision of something that's already happened,
然后就消失了
and then it's gone.
所以我知道斯利克的所在
That's how I knew where Slick was.
西斯科  太神奇了
Cisco, this is amazing.
我们要研究出该怎么做
We--we have to study this, figure out just what to do.
不不不  我们什么也不做
No, no, no, we're not doing any of that,
也不告诉任何人
and we're certainly not telling anybody, either.
西斯科  我以为你是
Cisco, I would think you'd be the one most intrigued
最想研究出它的原理的人
with knowing exactly what this is and how it works.
我看见了我不想看见的事
I'm seeing things I don't want to see.
知道了我不想知道的事
And knowing things I don't want to know.
我不想继续下去
I just want it to stop.
教授  我不想让任何人知道
Professor, I don't want anyone to know about this.
还不想
Not yet.
害怕是理所当然的
It's okay to be afraid, you know?
威尔斯告诉我这是我的未来
Wells told me this was my future.
他给了我这个能力
That he gave me this power.
但他却是个非常邪恶的人
But everything he did was evil.
我因此感到害怕  教授
That's what scares me, Professor.
向我保证
You have to promise me
你不会告诉任何人
you won't tell anyone about this.
我保证
I promise.
当我们成功
It appears that while we were indeed successful
关闭奇点时
in closing the singularity,
产生了不良的后果
there was an unfortunate side effect.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
通过电子图像
Using electrophotography,
我和西斯科寻找中城
Cisco and I were able to search Central City
是否有从别的空间
for any signs of energy entering our earth
进来的力量
from another dimension.
或如加里克先生所形容的"缺口"
From any breaches as Mr. Garrick described them.
当然  缺口不止一个
But, of course, there isn't just one breach.
一共有52个散布在全城
There's 52 of them scattered throughout the city.
这些缺口是时间和空间的口袋
These breaches are pockets of time and space
交错而成的
folded into and upon itself.
而最显著的缺口就是...
But the most significant breach of all appears to be
这个
this one.
它的具体位置在哪里
And where exactly is that located?
就在这里  尖端科研实验室
It's here, inside S.T.A.R. Labs.
越过了这个缺口
And just beyond that breach
就会是完全不同的...
is an entirely diff--fferent--
教授
Professor?
Professor!
非常欢迎你们来到
I'd like to personally welcome you
科学与技术
to the Scientific and Technological
尖端研究实验室
Advanced Research Laboratories,
它为为人所知的名称是
or, as it's more commonly known,
尖端科研实验室
S.T.A.R. Labs.
创立于1991年  尖端科研实验室
Founded in 1991, S.T.A.R. Labs is leading
主导世界开发新科技
the world in exciting new technological discoveries that,
我们的座右铭
as our motto suggests,
带我们走到了今天的明日世界
are truly bringing us tomorrow's world today.
我们专研人工智能
Specializing in artificial intelligence,
基因学  超能力...
genetics, and meta-human stu--
今天大家有眼福了
Oh, are we in for an unexpected treat.
我荣幸地介绍我们尖端科研实验室的
It is my absolute honor to introduce you to the founder
创始人
of S.T.A.R. Labs,
中城的救世主
the savior of Central City,
哈里森·威尔斯博士
Dr. Harrison Wells.